Sheet Music Collection
Sheet Music Collection
1842-1956
14 linear ft.
Collection of musical works and publications from many different sources. This includes printed sheet music, bound collections of music, books on music, books of music, opera programs, libretti, opera scores, church bulletins and announcements concerning musical performances, catalogues of music, and periodicals concerning music.
2751614
Biographical History
Most composers' biographies are easily available from other sources; therefore, the biographical history is limited to persons of note whose signatures appear on various items throughout this collection.
Thomas Mott Osborne (1859-1925) was a prison reformer and political reformer from Auburn, New York. In addition to his own signatures, those of his mother (Emily Osborne), sister (Eliza Osborne), and sons (David Munson Osborne II and Arthur Lithgow Osborne), appear on various items throughout this collection.
Winifred Seely Myers Love (1895-1994) was an alumna of Syracuse University who graduated with a degree in vocal performance from Crouse College. During her summers away from college she would teach music to high school students in Berwick, Pennsylvania. While her fiancé Frank Love was away serving during World War I, she served locally with the Red Cross and continued working to help soldiers throughout the rest of her life, hosting (with her husband) a recreation camp for soldiers on leave due to injuries in Thousand Island Park, New York. In 1990, she endowed a chair in the School of Arts & Sciences of Syracuse University, the first endowed chair in that school.
Frank Love (1889-1981), Winifred Love's husband, was also an alumnus of Syracuse University and its law school. He served as a member of the Board of Trustees at Syracuse University from the late 1960s to the mid 1970s. He was a charter member of American Legion Syracuse Post 41 and became State Commander in the American Legion in 1938.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Sheet Music Collection consists of musical works and publications from many different sources, including printed sheet music, bound collections of music, books on music, books of music, opera programs, libretti, opera scores, church bulletins and announcements concerning musical performances, catalogues of music, and periodicals concerning music.
Sheet music is limited to published sheet music with works by one composer or arranger within one opus or work. Bound collections of music are publisher-bound multiple-work or multiple-composer groupings of music. Books are publisher-bound books of music with specific purposes, whether instructionally- or institutionally-based. Opera items include opera programs, opera libretti, and scores from opera or large vocal works. Owner-bound sheet music is limited to sheet music items bound post-publication by the owners. Miscellaneous items include church bulletins, catalogues, periodicals, and other items which cannot otherwise be classified in this collection. Composer notoriety was determined by a poll of select music students, faculty, and librarians at Syracuse University and Gettysburg College.
Publishers represented in the collection include Boosey and Company, Edition Peters, C. F. Peters, Edward B. Marks Music Corporation, Theatre Magazine Company, Fred. Rullman, G. Ricordi and Company, Charles F. Tretbar, G. Schiermer, Oliver Ditson and Company, John W. Tufts, D. Appleton and Company, Root and Cady, White-Smith Music Publishing Company, Silver Burdett and Company, J. W. Smith, Jr., Maurice Schlesinger, J. Rieter-Biedermann, Universal-Edition, M. Witmark and Company, Theodore Presser Company, Uniôn Musical Española, R. H. Macy and Company, Leo Feist Incorporated, John Church Company, Carl Fischer, Thompson and Odell, Horace Waters, Au Ménestrel, Richard A. Saalfield, Harry Dichter, Ella Southwork Clark, Lee and Walkter, Boston Music Company, William A. Pond and Company, S. T. Gordon, J. F. Browne, E. H. Wade, Jaques and Brother, Clayton F. Summy Company, McKinley Music Company, L. D. Westfeldt, Daniels and Russell, E. T. Paull Music Company, Firth Pond and Company, F. A. North and Company, Lorenz Publishing Company, Abr. Lundquists, S. C. Jollie, Arthur P. Schmidt Company, Charivari, Belwin Incorporated, Novello and Company, Breitkopf and Härtel, N. Simrock, Jobin and Company, T. B. Harms, Johann Cappi, Offenbach a/M, Carl Rühle's Music-Verlag, and Irving Berlin Incorporated (among others).
Arrangement of the Collection
Materials are arranged by format initially and further arranged differently for each of the series. Sheet music is arranged by composer, separated by current notoriety (into well-known and lesser-known composers) and then arranged alphabetically. Bound collections of music are arranged by whether they are works mainly from one composer or multiple composers, with the single composers arranged by composer notoriety (into well-known and lesser-known composers) and further alphabetically and the multiple composers are arranged by instrument. Books are arranged by purpose (whether they are instructional or institutional e.g. hymnbooks), opera items are arranged by format again (whether they are programs, libretti, or scores), owner-bound sheet music is arranged by attribution alphabetically with unattributed items located at the end. Miscellaneous items are arranged by format.
Related Material
For more about the Osborne family, see the
Osborne Family Papers
. For more about the Clark Music Company, see the
Clark Music Company Records
.
Separated Material
Items printed in the Central New York area, some items concerning the portrayal of African-Americans, a published piece of sheet music from the original Wizard of Oz stage play by L. Frank Baum, and books of music reflective of specific cultures and times have been removed from this collection for cataloging. Please refer to to locate these items.
Subject and Genre Headings
Love, Frank C., 1889-1981.; Love, Winifred Seely Myers, 1895-1994.; Osborne, Arthur Lithgow.; Osborne, David Munson II.; Osborne, Eliza Wright.; Osborne, Thomas Mott, 1859-1926.; Irving Berlin, Inc.; Novello & Co.; Breitkopf & Härtel.; E. T. Paull Music Co.; Boston Music Co.; William A. Pond & Co.; Theodore Presser Company.; Silver Burdett Company.; M. Witmark & Sons.; John Church Company.; Carl Fischer Inc.; Boosey & Co.; Edition Peters.; C. F. Peters (firm); Ricordi (firm); Oliver Ditson Company.; G. Schirmer, Inc.; Instrumental music.; Operas -- Librettos.; Vocal music.; Sheet music -- Specimens.; United States -- Songs and music.; Sheet music.; Music books.; Music text-books.; Scores.; Programs (documents); Librettos (documents for music); Songbooks.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Unspecified.
Inventory
- Sheet music
  - Well-known composers
    - Beethoven, Ludwig Sonate für das Pianoforte, piano (solo) (Oversize 1)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig When Twilight Weaves, words by Gena Branscombe, arr. by Gena Branscombe, vocal (duet) (soprano and alto) two copies (Oversize 1)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig Sinfonien bearbeitet für Pianoforte, Violine und Violoncell: No. 1: Op. 21 in C., piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 1)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig Symphonie Pastorale à grand orchestra (Op. 68), arrangement for piano trio by C. G. Belcke (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 1)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig Sinfonien berbeitet für Pianoforte, violin und Violoncell: No. 5: Op. 67 in C m., v. Jul. André, piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 1)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig Fidelio: fantasie in Potpourri-Form für Pianoforte, piano solo (Oversize 1)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig Trios für Pianoforte, Violine und Violoncell, herausgegeben von Ferd. David, piano trios (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 1)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig Variationen und Rondo für Pianoforte und Violine, violin solo with piano accompaniment (Oversize 1)
    - Beethoven, Ludwig Berühmte Ouvertüren für Piano und Violine, violin solos with piano accompaniment (Oversize 1)
    - Bellini, Vincenzo Mira, o Norma / Hear Me, Norma, translated by Charles Jefferys, arranged by S. Nelson, vocal (duet with piano accompaniment) (two sopranos) (Oversize 1)
    - Bellini, Vincenzo March from Bellini's Celebrated Opera La Norma, arranged for the piano by Fred. Burgmüller, piano solo (signed "Jennie Lee") (Oversize 1)
    - Berlin, Irving All by Myself, vocal (song) (Oversize 1)
    - Berlin, Irving For Your Country and My Country, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 1)
    - Berlin, Irving Was There Ever a Pal Like You, vocal (song) (Oversize 1)
    - Berlioz, Hector Partitions à quatre mains: Roméo et Juliette, reduction by Camille Benoit, piano (four hands) (signed "T. M. Osborne" "July 1883") (Oversize 1)
    - Berlioz, Hector Partitions à quatre mains: Symphonie Fantastique, reduction by Ch. Bannelier, piano (four hands) (signed "T. M. Osborne" "July 1883") (Oversize 1)
    - Bizet, Georges Chanson du Toréador from Carmen, English version by Dr. Th. Baker vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 1)
    - Bizet, Georges Phantasie über Motive aus Carmen Oper in 4 Akten von Georges Bizet für Pianoforte und Violine, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 1)
    - Brahms, Johannes Trio (H dur) für Pianoforte, Violine und Violoncell (Op. 8), piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (Oversize 1)
    - Clementi, Muzio A Choice Selection from Gradus ad Parnassum by Muzio Clementi: 1st Part, piano (solo) (Oversize 1)
    - Chopin, Frédéric Funeral March, arr. T. H. Rollinson (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 1)
    - Donizetti, Gaetano Sweet the Moments, Rich in Blessing, arr. by J. Lincoln Hall, vocal (choral with organ accompaniment) (signed "Duval Dickson") (Oversize 1)
    - Donizetti, Gaetano Come è bello / Oh as Fair, from Lucrezia Borgia, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 1)
    - Donizetti, Gaetano The Land of Our Fathers / O Italia, words by Philip Edwards, arr. by Alfred J. Silver, Mus. Doc Dunelm, vocal (part-song for soprano, alto and baritone with piano accompaniment) three copies, each one of three separate J. Fischer & Brother editions (Oversize 1)
    - Dvorák, Antonin Songs My Mother Taught Me (Op. 55), words by Adolf Heyduk, translated by Natalia Macfarren, arranged by John Hyatt Brewer, vocal (choral with ad lib piano accompaniment) (Oversize 1)
    - Elgar, Edward Brothers, Alert!: Epilogue from "Caractacus", written by H. C. Acworth, C.I.E., vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 2)
    - Elgar, Edward My Love Dwelt in a Northern Land, words by Andrew Lang, vocal (choral) (piano accompaniment for practice only) (Oversize 2)
    - Elgar, Edward Salut d'amour, arr. by Alfred Roth (orchestral sheet music) (title covered with "Jimmy If You Love Me") (Oversize 2)
    - Gounod, Charles Ave Maria (Meditation), vocal (song with piano, organ, and violin accompaniment) (mezzo-soprano) (Oversize 2)
    - Gounod, Charles Choral Fantasia from Faust, arranged by N. Clifford Page, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 2)
    - Gounod, Charles Faites-lui mes aveux (from the opera "Faust"), English version by M. Louise Baum, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (alternate lyrics included) two copies (Oversize 2)
    - Gounod, Charles Où voulez-vous aller? (Tell Me, Fair maiden), English version by Mrs. John P. Morgan, vocal (song) (Oversize 2)
    - Gounod, Charles Soldiers Chorus from Faust, arr. by E. Bruck, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 2)
    - Gounod, Charles Unfold, Ye Portals! From The Redeption, vocal (choral with piano or organ accompaniment) (Oversize 2)
    - Handel, George Frideric Hallelujah Chorus from The "Messiah", vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 2)
    - Handel, George Frideric Hear Me! Ye Winds and Waves/Tutta Raccolta Ancor, English translation by Theo. Marzials, arranged by A. L., vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (low voice) (Oversize 2)
    - Haydn, Joseph Bind' auf dein Haar / My mother bids me bind my hair, vocal (song) (soprano) (Oversize 2)
    - Haydn, Joseph Trios für Pianoforte, Violine und Violoncell, piano trios (piano, violin, cello) (cello part only) (signed David M. Osborne) (Oversize 2)
    - Haydn, Joseph Variations pour le piano-forte sur le theme "Gott erhalte den Kaifer", piano (solo) (includes lyrics in statement of theme) (Oversize 2)
    - Herbert, Victor Ah! Sweet Mystery of Life (The Dream Melody): For It Is Love Alone That Rules for Aye! from Naughty Marietta, lyric by Rida Johnson Young vocal (song) (Oversize 2)
    - Herbert, Victor Selection from the Comic Opera Mlle Modiste, arranged for orchestra by Otto Langey (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 2)
    - Herbert, Victor Waltzes from Babes in Toyland, arr. by Karl L. Hoschna piano (solo) (Oversize 2)
    - Jaques-Dalcroze, Emile L'oiseau bleu (Op. 74), Poésie de A. LL. Hettisch, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (signed by Winifred S. Myers) (Oversize 2)
    - Kern, Jerome D'ye Love Me?, words by Otto Harbach and Oscar Hammerstein II, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 2)
    - Liszt, Franz Rhapsodies hongroises pour piano No. 14: A. H. G. de Bülow, arranged by E. G. Jansen, piano (four hands) (signed "Thomas M. Osborne" "December 1884") (Oversize 2)
    - Liszt, Franz Symphonische Dichtungen für Grosses Orchester No. 3: Les Préludes, piano (four hands) (signed "T. M. Osborne" "Sept 1883") (Oversize 2)
    - Liszt, Franz Von der Wiege bis zum Grabe symphonische Dichtung nach einer Leichnung von Michael Zichy / Du berceau jusqu'à la tombe Poème symphonique d'apres un dessin de Michel Zichy, piano (four hands) (Oversize 2)
    - Mascagni, Pietro Intermezzo (from Cavalleria Rusticana/Rustic Chivalry), simplified arrangement by Launce Knight, piano (solo) (Oversize 2)
    - Mascagni, Pietro Introduction and Hymn to the Sun for Chorus and Orchestra from the opera "Iris", English text by F. E. Weatherly vocal (choral) (choral parts only) two copies (Oversize 2)
    - Massenet, Jules Scènes Pittoresques: 4eme Suite d'Orchestre, piano (four hands) (signed "T. M. Osborne" "Sept. 1883") (Oversize 2)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix Mendelssohn's Four-Part Songs: The Only Complete Edition, vocal (choral a cappella) two copies (Oversize 2)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix Intermezzo from F. Mendelssohn's "Midsummer Night's Dream", arr. by W. F. Kretschmer (orchestral sheet music) (also contains sheet music for "Noctorno" from the same piece) (Oversize 2)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix "Midsummer Night's Dream" Overture, arr. by Theo. Moses-Tobani (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 2)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix Rondo capriccio (Op. 14): Kochzeitsmarsch, Kriegsmarsch, Trauermarsch und 14 Lieder ohne Worte für Pianoforte, abdruck aus der Gesammtausgabe von Ed. Mertke, piano (solo) (signed "Cora D. Graham" "Syracuse" "New York" [outside cover] "Cora M. Dodson" "Leipsic, Germany" "1897-8" [first page of sheet music]) (Oversize 2)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix Sonate für Pianoforte und Violine (Op. 4), violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 2)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix Spring Song, words by Arthur J. Lamb, arr. by Rudolf Thaler, vocal (song) (Oversize 2)
    - Mendelssohn, Felix Wedding March from Summernight's Dream, (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 2)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus Gloria in Excelsis, from 12th Mass, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies, one signed "TMOsborne," the other marked "Piano" (Oversize 2)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus Gloria from Mozart's 12th Mass, arr. by Theo. Moses (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 2)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus Oh! Isis and Osiris, guide them / O Isis und Osiris, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (bass) (Oversize 2)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus Ouverture zu Oper "Don Juan" für Pianoforte zu 2 Händen, piano (solo) (Oversize 2)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus Messe in G dur, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) (soprano, alto, tenor, bass solos) two copies (Oversize 2)
    - Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus Requiem Mass, vocal (choral with keyboard accompaniment) (soprano, alto, tenor, bass solos) (Oversize 2)
    - Offenbach, Jacques The Commodore: Nautical Opera in Three Acts, libretto by H. B. Farnie and R. Reece, vocal (songs with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 3)
    - Offenbach, Jacques O Belle Nuit: Barcarole from J. Offenbach's Comic Opera Contes d'Hoffmann, arr. by Alfred Roth (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 3)
    - Offenbach, Jacques Orpheus in der Unterwelt / Orphée aux Enfers: Overture, arr. by Charles J. Roberts (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 3)
    - Offenbach, Jacques Orpheus Overture, arr. by George L. Tracy (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 3)
    - Puccini, Giacomo As thro' the Street (Musetta's Valse Song) from "The Bohemians" / "La Bohème", vocal (song) (medium voice) (Oversize 3)
    - Purcell, Henry Nymphs and Shepherds: the Libertine, words by Thomas Shadwell, accompaniment by Myles B. Foster, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (mezzo-soprano or baritone) (Oversize 3)
    - Purcell, Henry Purcell's Ground with Variations for the Piano Forte, piano (solo) (Oversize 3)
    - Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolai Scheherazade d'après "Mille et une nuits": suite symphonique pour orchestra (Op. 35), piano (four hands) (Oversize 3)
    - Rubinstein, Anton Ballet Suite from the opera Feramors, arr. by Charles J. Roberts (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 3)
    - Rubinstein, Anton Ballettmusik und Hochzeitszug / Ballet music and Wedding March: from the opera "Feramors", edited and fingered by Louis Oesterle, piano (four hands) (signed "TMOsborne") (Oversize 3)
    - Rubinstein, Anton "Wedding Procession" from Opera: "Feramors", arr. by Theo. Moses (orchestral sheet music) (also contains "Dance of the Bayaderes" from the same opera) (Oversize 3)
    - Rubinstein, Anton Ballet Music from the Opera of The Demon, piano (four hands) (Oversize 3)
    - Rubinstein, Anton Océan: 2ième Symphonie (G dur) pour Orchestre (Op. 42), dédiée à François Liszt, piano (four hands) (Oversize 3)
    - Rubinstein, Anton Symphonie dramatique (No. 4, D moll) pour Orchestre (Op. 95), piano (four hands) (Oversize 3)
    - Saint-Saëns, Camille Lord, in this Thy mercy's day, words by I. Williams, adapted by Edward Shippen Barnes, vocal (song with piano or organ accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 3)
    - Saint-Saëns, Camille Le Rouet d'Omphale: Poëme Symphonique (Op. 31), piano (four hands) (signed "T. M. Osborne" "July 1883") (Oversize 3)
    - Saint-Saëns, Camille Septuor (Op. 65), pour piano à 4 mains par G. Fauré, piano (four hands) (Oversize 3)
    - Saint-Saëns, Camille Suite Algérienne (Op. 60), à 4 mains par G. Fauré, piano (four hands) (Oversize 3)
    - Schubert, Franz Ausgemählte Lieder von Franz Schubert für Violoncell und Piano, bearbeitet von Georg Goltermann, cello (solo with piano accompaniment) (piano part only) (Oversize 3)
    - Schubert, Franz Coronach: Chorus for Three Female Voices, lyrics from Sir Walter Scott's "Lady of the Lake," vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (three female voices) published by Novello, Ewer and Co., two copies, one signed "TM Osborne," one marked "Piano," (Oversize 3)
    - Schubert, Franz Coronach: Chorus for Three Female Voices, lyrics from Sir Walter Scott's "Lady of the Lake," vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (three female voices) published by Oliver Ditson Co., two copies (Oversize 3)
    - Schubert, Franz Der Einsame, Gedicht v. Carl Lappe in Musik gesetzt für eine Singstimme mit Begleit des Pianoforte (Op. 41), vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (Oversize 3)
    - Schubert, Franz Her Portrait / Ihr Bild, lyrics by Heinrich Heine, translated by Arthur Westbrook, vocal (song with piano accompaniment) (high voice) (signed "Winifred Seely Myers" "Nescopeck, Penn'a") (Oversize 3)
    - Schubert, Franz Notturno (Es dur) für pianoforte, Violine und Violoncell (Op. 148), piano trio (piano, violin, and cello) (Oversize 3)
    - Schubert, Franz Sérénade de Schubert ("Leise flehen") pour violon et piano, violin (solo with piano accompaniment) (violin part only) (Oversize 3)
    - Schubert, Franz Trios für Pianoforte, Violine und Violoncell, piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (trios from Op.99, 100, and 148) (Oversize 3)
    - Schubert, Franz Trios für Pianoforte, Violine und Violoncell, piano trio (piano, violin, cello) (trios from Op.99, 100, and 148) (Oversize 4)
    - Schubert, Franz Impromptu (Op. 142), keyboard (solo) (Oversize 4)
    - Schubert, Franz Messe No. 4, C dur (Op. 48), arranged by Ebenezer Prout, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) (soprano, alto, tenor, bass solos) (Oversize 4)
    - Schubert, Franz Serenade, arr. by Max Vogrich, vocal (choral with piano accompaniment) two copies (Oversize 4)
    - Schumann, Robert Quintett für Pianoforte, zwei Violinen, viola und Violoncello (Op. 44), arr. Clara Schumann piano quintet (piano, 2 violins, viola, cello) (cello part only) (Oversize 4)
    - Schumann, Robert Quintett für Pianoforte, 2 Violinen, Viola und Violoncell (Op. 44), arrangement für das Pianoforte zu vier Händen von Clara Schumann, piano (four hands) (Oversize 4)
    - Sousa, John Philip El Capitan, (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 4)
    - Sousa, John Philip George Washington Bicentennial March, Written in Commemoration of the Two Hundredth Anniversary of the Birth of George Washington, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 4)
    - Sousa, John Philip The High School Cadets' March, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 4)
    - Sousa, John Philip The Liberty Loan: March Past of the 40th U. S. Infantry, piano (solo) (Oversize 4)
    - Sousa, John Philip The Stars and Stripes Forever, (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 4)
    - Sousa, John Philip Washington Post March, (orchestral sheet music) (with sheet music for "Our Flirtation March" on the back) (Oversize 4)
    - Strauss, Johann I, Loreley Rhein-Klänge (Op. 154), (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 4)
    - Strauss, Eduard, Giroflé-Girofla Waltz (Op. 123), keyboard (solo) (Oversize 4)
    - Strauss, Johann II Beautiful Blue Danube Waltz, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 4)
    - Strauss, Johann II Blue Danube Waltz, (orchestral sheet music) (includes hand-written horns parts) (Oversize 4)
    - Strauss, Johann II High Life Waltz, keyboard (solo) (Oversize 4)
    - Strauss, Johann II Indigo-Marsch (Op. 349), (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 4)
    - Strauss, Johann II Overture to the Operetta "Die Fledermaus" (the Bat), arr. by Ross Jungnickel (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 4)
    - Strauss, Johann II Pásmán-Walzer from Ritter Pásmán, Komische Oper in 3 Akten, piano (four hands) (Oversize 4)
    - Strauss, Johann II Postillon d'amour: polka française (Op. 317), (orchestral sheet music) (several parts handwritten) (Oversize 4)
    - Strauss, Johann II "You and You" Waltz from Comic Opera: "The Bat" (Fledermaus) (Op. 367), (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 4)
    - Sullivan, Arthur Selection from A. Sullivan's Comic Opera The Gondoliers, arr. Theo. Moses (Op. 166) (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 4)
    - Sullivan, Arthur Selection from A. Sullivan's Comic Opera The Gondoliers, Revised by Julius S. Seredy, arr. Theo. Moses (Op. 166) (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 4)
    - Sullivan, Arthur Selection "Iolanthe" (from Arthur Sullivan's comic Opera), arr. E. N. Catlin (Op. 110) (orchestral sheet music) (Oversize 4)
    - Sullivan, Arthur The Lost Chord, vocal (song) (signed by Lois Secor) (Oversize 4)
    - Sullivan, Arthur Looking Back, vocal (song) (Oversize 4)